# Mariana

Graphic Design, Digital Design and Creative Coding Coimbra, Portugal



# da Silva

I enjoy creating meaningful experiences through design and technology, and I'm interested in exploring new opportunities to apply my skills, contribute to innovative projects and look for new methods to express my creativity. In my free time, you can find me playing chess or walking around while listening to podcasts.

### **EDUCATION**

SET. 2021 – SET. 2023 Master in Design and Multimedia in University of Coimbra

SET. 2018 – JUL. 2021 Bachelor in Design and Multimedia in University of Coimbra

SET. 2015 — JUL. 2018 Visual Arts at Escola Sencundária Marques Castilho

## CO-CURRICULAR

Núcleo de Estudantes de Informática da Universidade de Coimbra

JUN. 2022 – JUN. 2023 President of the Plenary Board and Image Collaborator for the Shift Appens hackthon

JUN. 2021 — JUN. 2022 Secretary to the Board

SET. 2020 — JUN. 2021 Coordinator of External Relations and Professional Opportunities

### **EXPERIENCE**

NOV. 2022 - SET. 2023 (part-time)

## Lead Designer Queima das Fitas de Coimbra 2023

I led a team of five in producing the visual identity for the 2023 edition of the event. This included creating the logo, designing templates for communication on different media and platforms, and guiding the application on various media, such as social media posts, promotional videos, merchandising, banners and posters.

JAN. 2021 - JUN. 2021 (freelance)

# Designer

# Band La Palisse - Logo, 1st cd jewel and album

Besides creating the official logo for the Portuguese band, I designed their first album, including the album cover, CD jewel, booklet, planning the CD for sale and application on platforms such as Spotify.

SET. 2019 — MAR. 2020 (part-time, remote)

## Designer

## Init Brand - Production of Merchandising

Production of advertising and merchandising. During this period I produced graphic material for more than twenty secondary school lists and other similar requests.

### SKILLS Technical - Soft

Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Indesign
Adobe After Effects
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Premiere pro
Blender
Cinema 4D
Processing.org
HTML, CSS, Javascript
Slack, Trello, Figma, Notion
Brand identity
Content creating
Conceptualisation

Friendly
Teamwork
Communication
Planning
Problem solving
Creative
Adaptable
Attention to detail

## in Bē 🗘

@marianassilvas amarianatavaresdasilva@gmail.com

## LANGUAGES

Visual communication Photo/video editing

Portuguese (native)

English (fluent)